Okay, what up, y'all? We're back with a
brand new video. Make sure you like and
subscribe on school if you appreciate
the content. Uh listen,
we are back and we're back with a
banger. Today, we have the consistent
room workflow.
Uh this will essentially let you uh have
a consistent background
uh across uh all your images if that's
what you're trying to do.
>> [music]
>> Um obviously,
uh there's a lot many parts to it, but
the idea is that uh you generate a room
uh image
uh and then you create multiple angles
of that room uh with flux client. And
then uh we use a flux client again to
add the character directly in uh the
generated images.
So, that's kind of the idea behind the
whole pipeline. You will need a flux uh
client Laura to make it work as good as
it can work. Uh if you don't have one,
I'll have a full tutorial on uh the
school showing you exactly how to do it.
Yeah, that's pretty much it. Um I'll go
every part and that's going to be it.
So, let's get it.
Okay, so the first part here uh we
generate an image with
Quen image. Now, you could use uh flux
client to do the the image, too. Okay,
that's totally possible, but uh I would
say the quality of um the room generated
with Quen image is significantly better
than what uh client can generate. So,
kind of have to choose. Obviously, uh
Quen is uh significantly bigger, so
might be a harder to run depending on
your PC.
Uh so, yeah, you make your choice. You
have both uh options here. I'll put the
links to all the models like I always
do. Uh and yeah, so after you have your
room, uh and you can also grab a room
from Pinterest, for example, and just
upload it and use it as uh the reference
for the angles. That's also an option.
>> [snorts]
>> Um so, yeah.
Once you have your room, uh we are going
to generate multiple angles of that same
room. Uh this is using flux client and
uh
you know, different settings. So, here
as we can see,
let me just grab the original so we can
do a quick comparison.
Um
this image right here is exactly, I
mean, really, really close to what we
see here.
Uh and client is pretty much the only
model that can do this right now. Maybe
flux dev can do it, but it's really not
like easy to run for most people, so uh
that flux client is able to do this is
pretty interesting. This angle is going
to be uh what? A zoomed out angle from
the bed. So, here we basically zoomed in
on the bed and then it kept [music]
everything consistent uh compared to the
original image. Even the gibberish text
is still gibberish, so so that's that's
good. That's going to be one of the
issues, too.
Uh
if you don't generate with something
like nano banana or you use a real image
as your base, you might struggle with
stuff like text on posters and like
that. That will be an issue. So, you
kind of have to choose where do you want
to get your base image um when you start
the workflow.
This uh shot is a low angle of the room.
So, it's basically in the middle of the
room uh and as we can see, it's pretty
consistent again. Uh everything is at
the same place, even the stuff that's
really far away. [music] You can see
that it keeps uh the same position and
the same kind of uh shape.
So, I think it's pretty good, to be
honest.
And then here we have daytime shots, so
we have [music] uh lighting com- coming
from uh the window and stuff.
So, and it stays consistent again, and
this is another uh shot from um
the bed. So,
as we can see, the angles part of the
workflow works pretty well.
Uh obviously, it will significantly
depend on uh the base image you give it.
So, just kind of kind of keep that in
mind. So, after that, we have the actual
image generation here. Um
you have a couple of options for that,
so you can plug in uh your um
final image [music] directly in uh the
workflow uh to use it as your reference
background. Uh in this example, I'm
going to use this image and then I'm
going to prompt [music] uh here.
Like I said, I have a Laura trained on
my uh character, so this is what's going
to be used [music] to generate the
likeness of the person. Uh if you don't
have one, you have two options. You make
a Laura and I'll have a guide uh on the
school or uh you do a face swap with
something like reactor or whatever, you
know, face swap uh solution you have.
And
uh that's kind of your two options here.
Or if you have a Laura trained on
another model, you can do a face swap
using your Laura. That's also an option.
I'm not going to cover this in this
video, but this is also an option for
you.
Okay, so here we're going to prompt it
uh and then uh run it just to see if we
get, you know, the the proper daytime
image. Uh so, here we have a young wo-
young woman taking a far away mirror
selfie. This assumes that the mirror is
not visible in the image.
Uh obviously, you can put the mirror
pretty much wherever you want, to be
honest. It doesn't really matter. Um and
then you can describe the character. So,
she has long black hair and is wearing
intricate black knight armor. Um this
can be changed to whatever you need, to
be honest. So, here I can just say um
is wearing a pumpkin
inflatable inflatable
uh suit.
And she's taking the picture with a
black iPhone 15 Pro. Um [music]
I like to specify the phone so that we
can get uh you know, a consistent phone
across all the images when we use a
phone, right? Just makes sense to me.
So, after all this is done, we can just
run the prompt and we are going to see
uh the base result here. So, as we can
see already, she is in a daytime
environment. All the posters are
consistent. If we go back and grab the
image,
we can see that a client uh perfectly
incorporated the character inside the
image and it looks like seamless, right?
It looks like it's real
uh and most most of the details in the
background and stuff are still [music]
consistent. So, I would say that's uh
you know, a good example of the workflow
working. Uh and then I added a face
detailer part because [music]
um the likeness is not always the best.
So, here we can just run this. Let me
just lock the seed here so we can keep
the image.
And then
uh this is what I did prior.
>> [music]
>> Uh we just run that. Okay, so this is
what we got.
Uh I think the lighting is a little bit
better, but it could be better, too.
And we can do multiple
uh tests here, so I can just change the
prompt and change the image just to kind
of prove it that it does work. Um so,
I'll use the low angle shot here. So,
I'll just grab the latent directly and
plug it in the room thing.
>> [music]
>> Uh let me just make sure I got it,
though.
So, you plug it in the room and then you
can just ask for whatever. So, here I'm
going to say
uh young woman taking
a selfie. Uh
she is squatting
in um
she's squatting. Let's just say that.
Let's just try that.
Not sure what it's going to give, but
let's just see.
Okay, so she is squatting. Um she is in
the same room. The same room seems to be
consistent again. Obviously, she has two
phones, [music] so this is an issue.
Uh the cool thing, though, is that you
can just run it again. You can just run
it again and uh
you might get something different. You
will get something different, actually,
every single time. Just cuz that's just
how it works, but um
Okay, so as we can see here, we got a
selfie in the exact same room. Uh she's
just squatting wearing that whatever
pumpkin outfit uh they gave her. And uh
all the rest, all the posters,
everything in the background is still
consistent with the original image. And
yeah, uh let's try something else. Um
let's see here. So, like I said, you
grab it from uh the latent directly and
you [music] plug it in
the room uh conditioning
and then you run it. Uh I'm going to
change the prompt here. I don't want to
necessarily have the squatting again.
Um
I'm just going to say that uh she is
posing
in
uh the room
behind the chair.
Okay, so just say that. Let's see. Okay,
so she's in the same room again. She
does look pretty tall, but I don't
really have a fix for that, to be
honest.
You can just run it again, probably, and
the the the height will be changed.
There is not a good fix for that though,
to be honest. It's still a little bit
inconsistent, and
that's because the model does not
understand height and stuff like that
really good.
But yeah,
obviously this is a weird result, I'm
not going to lie.
We can do it
better prompt maybe, maybe not refer to
the chair since she's interacted with
it.
Let's just try that here.
As you can see, we have
you know, the same room again.
Everything is consistent. Obviously, the
costume is not going to be consistent
because we do not pass it as reference
latent.
>> [music]
>> But I do have the workflow that lets you
create multiple angles using flux line
too.
>> [music]
>> So, everything is covered pretty much.
And then I could run the face detailer.
The issue with the face detailer is that
it's going to find every single face in
your image, which means if you have
posters, it's also going to try and face
detail with [music] the Laura on the
posters.
So yeah, not ideal, obviously.
And then
we have this part here. So, if you want
to use an image that we already
generated before, and we don't want to
use those generated images specifically,
you can just go ahead and use this part
and
just plug it in the room directly.
And then
you run it, and you should be getting
the room there with
the character in it.
Right? It's just supposed to work. It
just works, as you can see.
So yeah, the idea is that you grab an
image,
you make multiple angles of it, and then
you can use those
for your generations with a Laura or
face swapping if that's what you want to
do. So, I'm going to stop there. Um
everything's going to be available on
the school community, so make sure you
join and subscribe if you want the the
full fledged version.
The free version is still going to be,
you know,
more than capable of doing whatever you
need. The the sub versions is going to
have a little bit more options.
So yeah, shout out to everybody who
supports me, man. I appreciate you guys,
and I will see you in the next one.
Peace.